<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>I think I&#39;ve got it... on I think I&#39;ve got it...</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in I think I&#39;ve got it... on I think I&#39;ve got it...</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Gaining Intuition for Idenitification Constraints in Bayesian IRT Models: Part I</title>
      <link>/post/gaining-intuition-for-idenitification-constraints-in-bayesian-irt-models-part-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/gaining-intuition-for-idenitification-constraints-in-bayesian-irt-models-part-i/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I’ve spent considerable time developing JAGS/Stan code for fitting Bayesian IRT models. Understanding (let alone resolving) identification constraints has to be one of the most frustrating stages in the workflow. I think this is largely because constraints are already configured in the software we use to implement IRT analyses, so there’s just little reason to know the details! But for those of you who’ve fit latent variable models as Bayesian hierarchical models, you’ll know that understanding &lt;em&gt;why&lt;/em&gt; such constraints are necessary, &lt;em&gt;what&lt;/em&gt; options are available for model identification, and &lt;em&gt;what&lt;/em&gt; their implications are for parameter interpretation can be really confusing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Even if you haven’t had to manually identify an IRT model before, it’s worth gaining intuition for it for at least 3 reasons:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol style=&#34;list-style-type: decimal&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It’s good to understand the defaults that a particular software/package provides, especially when making comparisons;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It’s really helpful (and more important!) when you move to more complex models, such as explanatory or multidimensional IRT models;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Latent variable models are inherently ambiguous, and identifying the metric on which parameters lie is a great exercise in becoming more comfortable with them.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the first of (at least) two posts, I’m going to cover identification for a few of the more common IRT models. I’ll touch on constraints conceptually, but the real goal is to &lt;em&gt;show&lt;/em&gt; you different ways of identifying IRT models in JAGS. I’ll focus on a few things with each example:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Why constraints are necessary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Different options for setting constraints&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Why we might (not) want to use a given set of constraints&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before diving in, it’s important to stress that &lt;strong&gt;identification is a property of the likelihood model&lt;/strong&gt;, and thus, despite this post focusing on a Bayesian approach, it applies to frequentist methods as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;irt-models-for-binary-responses&#34; class=&#34;section level2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;IRT Models for Binary Responses&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;i.-rasch-model&#34; class=&#34;section level3&#34;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;I. Rasch Model&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let’s start with the simplest of IRT models. Letting &lt;span class=&#34;math inline&#34;&gt;\(i\)&lt;/span&gt; index individuals, and &lt;span class=&#34;math inline&#34;&gt;\(j\)&lt;/span&gt; index items, the Rasch model specifies the log-odds of a correct respone as the difference between an individual’s latent trait &lt;span class=&#34;math inline&#34;&gt;\(\theta_i\)&lt;/span&gt; and item’s difficulty &lt;span class=&#34;math inline&#34;&gt;\(\beta_j\)&lt;/span&gt;. Let’s denote this difference &lt;span class=&#34;math inline&#34;&gt;\(\eta_{ij}\)&lt;/span&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;math display&#34;&gt;\[ \text{logit}\big\{p\big(y_{ij} = 1 | \Theta\big)\big\} = \theta_i - \beta_j = \eta_{ij}.\]&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;is-this-model-identified&#34; class=&#34;section level4&#34;&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Is this model identified?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The answer, of course, is no. The issue here is one that plagues all latent variable models—there is no inherent metric when we’re measuring unobserved variables, and so identifying a unique solution (i.e., obtaining parameter estimates) is impossible without first imposing a scale via constraints.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The issue is made evident when we consider the difference &lt;span class=&#34;math inline&#34;&gt;\(\eta_{ij}\)&lt;/span&gt;. Note that an endless number of solutions for &lt;span class=&#34;math inline&#34;&gt;\(\theta_i\)&lt;/span&gt; and &lt;span class=&#34;math inline&#34;&gt;\(\beta_j\)&lt;/span&gt; result in the same &lt;span class=&#34;math inline&#34;&gt;\(\eta_{ij}\)&lt;/span&gt; (and by extension, likelihood). In the literature, this is often referred to as &lt;em&gt;additive&lt;/em&gt; aliasing—adding the same constant to both &lt;span class=&#34;math inline&#34;&gt;\(\theta_i\)&lt;/span&gt; and &lt;span class=&#34;math inline&#34;&gt;\(\beta_j\)&lt;/span&gt; results in the same likelihood.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To make this really clear, suppose the “true” value of &lt;span class=&#34;math inline&#34;&gt;\(\eta_{11}\)&lt;/span&gt; is &lt;span class=&#34;math inline&#34;&gt;\(2\)&lt;/span&gt;. Well, setting &lt;span class=&#34;math inline&#34;&gt;\(\theta_1 = 3\)&lt;/span&gt; and &lt;span class=&#34;math inline&#34;&gt;\(\beta_1 = 1\)&lt;/span&gt; results in &lt;span class=&#34;math inline&#34;&gt;\(\eta_{11}=3 - 1 =2\)&lt;/span&gt;. But setting &lt;span class=&#34;math inline&#34;&gt;\(\theta_1=102\)&lt;/span&gt; and &lt;span class=&#34;math inline&#34;&gt;\(\beta_1=100\)&lt;/span&gt; also leads to &lt;span class=&#34;math inline&#34;&gt;\(\eta_{11} = 102-100=2\)&lt;/span&gt;. And for that matter, &lt;span class=&#34;math inline&#34;&gt;\(\eta_{11} = -3 - -5 = 2\)&lt;/span&gt;, and &lt;span class=&#34;math inline&#34;&gt;\(\eta_{11} = 2.3 - 0.3 = 2\)&lt;/span&gt;, and &lt;span class=&#34;math inline&#34;&gt;\(\eta_{11} = 3,222 - 3,000 = 2\)&lt;/span&gt;, and on we go on an endless quest to find a unique solution to an impossible mathematical problem.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;how-do-we-identify-this-model&#34; class=&#34;section level4&#34;&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;How do we identify this model?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Because we’re interested in the &lt;em&gt;relative&lt;/em&gt; difference between the latent trait and item difficulty, what we need is an anchoring point that will impose a metric and allow a unique solution to be found. There are &lt;em&gt;many&lt;/em&gt; options for constraining the model, but I’ll focus on those most common in the psychometric literature:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol style=&#34;list-style-type: decimal&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Constraining the mean and variance of the latent trait distribution, such that &lt;span class=&#34;math inline&#34;&gt;\(\theta_i \sim \mathcal{N}\big(0, 1\big)\)&lt;/span&gt; for all &lt;span class=&#34;math inline&#34;&gt;\(i\)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Constraining the mean of the item difficulties&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;ii.-two-parameter-logistic-2pl-model&#34; class=&#34;section level3&#34;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;II. Two-Parameter Logistic (2PL) Model&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;math display&#34;&gt;\[ \text{logit}\big\{p\big(y_{ij} = 1 | \Theta\big)\big\} = \alpha_j\big(\theta_i - \beta_j\big) = \eta_{ij}.\]&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;irt-models-for-multinomialordinal-responses&#34; class=&#34;section level2&#34;&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;IRT Models for Multinomial/Ordinal Responses&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div id=&#34;graded-response-model&#34; class=&#34;section level3&#34;&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Graded Response Model&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gaining Intuition for Identification Constraints in Bayesian IRT Models: Part I</title>
      <link>/tutorial/example/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tutorial/example/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve spent considerable time developing JAGS/Stan code for fitting Bayesian IRT models. Understanding (let alone resolving) identification constraints has to be one of the most frustrating stages in the workflow. I think this is largely because constraints are already configured in the software we use to implement these models, so there&amp;rsquo;s just little reason to know the details! For those of us who work within a Bayesian framework, however, when it comes time to identify our model, it&amp;rsquo;s an inevitable trip to Google, and/or trial-and-error until we &lt;em&gt;hope&lt;/em&gt; that our solutions worked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;ll start off with a simple Rasch model:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;$$ \text{logit}\Big(p\big(y_{ij} = 1 \big)\Big) = \theta_i - \beta_j, $$&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;which specifies the log-odds of a correct response for individual $i$ to binary item $j$ as the difference between their latent trait $\theta_i$ and the difficulty of the item $\beta_j$.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/privacy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Example Talk</title>
      <link>/talk/example/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talk/example/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-note&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Click on the &lt;strong&gt;Slides&lt;/strong&gt; button above to view the built-in slides feature.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Slides can be added in a few ways:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Create&lt;/strong&gt; slides using Academic&amp;rsquo;s &lt;em&gt;Slides&lt;/em&gt; feature and link using &lt;code&gt;url_slides&lt;/code&gt; parameter in the front matter of the talk file&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Upload&lt;/strong&gt; an existing slide deck to &lt;code&gt;static/&lt;/code&gt; and link using &lt;code&gt;url_slides&lt;/code&gt; parameter in the front matter of the talk file&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Embed&lt;/strong&gt; your slides (e.g. Google Slides) or presentation video on this page using &lt;a href=&#34;https://sourcethemes.com/academic/docs/writing-markdown-latex/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;shortcodes&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Further talk details can easily be added to this page using &lt;em&gt;Markdown&lt;/em&gt; and $\rm \LaTeX$ math code.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>/project/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/research/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;overview&#34;&gt;Overview&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve spent the better part of the last four years developing extensions to the hierarchical rater model (HRM), a latent variable modeling framework for the analysis of ratings data. In conjunction with Drs. Jodi Casabianca (Educational Testing Services, previously UT-Austin) and Brian Junker (Carnegie Mellon), this work has focused on developing theory, generating code for fitting Bayesian models, empirically testing these methods via Monte Carlo simulations, and disseminating the work through research articles and conference workshops. Keep reading to learn a bit more about the HRM, and the work I&amp;rsquo;m completing as part of my dissertation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;hierarchical-rater-models&#34;&gt;Hierarchical Rater Models&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ratings are ubiquitous in psychological measurement&amp;mdash;performance appraisals in the industry rely on ratings collected from supervisors, therapists complete observational inventories to measure psychological traits, and essays from standardized tests are scored by raters trained on rating rubrics. From a measurement perspective, ratings are fundamentally flawed because they rely on subjective judgement. Idiosyncratic rater behavior introduces a form of measurement error, collectively called &lt;em&gt;rater effects&lt;/em&gt;, that compromises the integrity of final scores used to describe the subject of those ratings. This is clearly problematic, given that assessments are designed to be fair, and final scores are often tied to high-stakes decisions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The HRM framework was developed as a way to simultaneously describe individual rater behavior and provide measurement of individuals&amp;rsquo; psychological traits while correcting for rater effects. Besides providing more accurate and reliable measurement, by capturing rater behavior, it encourages ongoing assessment of raters&amp;rsquo; performance, which can be used to inform future rater trainings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/img/stages.png&#34; alt=&#34;Stages of the HRM&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The HRM is a latent variable model composed of two separate modeling stages, which highlight the &lt;em&gt;hierarchical&lt;/em&gt; structure of the rating process. The first stage is a signal detection model for observed ratings $x$ that produces as its output a measure of rater severity/leniency error, rater variability, as well as an ideal score $\xi$ (the score the individual would have received from a perfect rater with no bias). The second stage is an item response theory (IRT) model, which takes these ideal ratings (corrected for rater effects), and produces estimates of the latent trait of interest $\theta$ (e.g., depression, writing procifiency).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Extensions of this basic model have been made to accommodate multidimensional structure in rating instruments, time series and longitudinal ratings, and inclusion of covariates of the rating process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;my-research&#34;&gt;My Research&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My work on the HRM includes the development of the HRM for multidimensional rating rubrics (paper just submitted!), as well as the evaluation of the HRM for rater covariates (my dissertation).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re interested in more on the mechanics of the HRM, stay tuned for upcoming tutorials.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Person Re-Identification System For Mobile Devices</title>
      <link>/publication/person-re-id/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/person-re-id/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;More detail can easily be written here using &lt;em&gt;Markdown&lt;/em&gt; and $\rm \LaTeX$ math code.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mobile visual clothing search</title>
      <link>/publication/clothing-search/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/clothing-search/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;More detail can easily be written here using &lt;em&gt;Markdown&lt;/em&gt; and $\rm \LaTeX$ math code.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slides</title>
      <link>/slides/example-slides/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/slides/example-slides/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;welcome-to-slides&#34;&gt;Welcome to Slides&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://sourcethemes.com/academic/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Academic&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;features&#34;&gt;Features&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Efficiently write slides in Markdown&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3-in-1: Create, Present, and Publish your slides&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Supports speaker notes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mobile friendly slides&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;controls&#34;&gt;Controls&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Next: &lt;code&gt;Right Arrow&lt;/code&gt; or &lt;code&gt;Space&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous: &lt;code&gt;Left Arrow&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Start: &lt;code&gt;Home&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Finish: &lt;code&gt;End&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Overview: &lt;code&gt;Esc&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Speaker notes: &lt;code&gt;S&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fullscreen: &lt;code&gt;F&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Zoom: &lt;code&gt;Alt + Click&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/hakimel/reveal.js#pdf-export&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;PDF Export&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;code&gt;E&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;code-highlighting&#34;&gt;Code Highlighting&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Inline code: &lt;code&gt;variable&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Code block:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-python&#34;&gt;porridge = &amp;quot;blueberry&amp;quot;
if porridge == &amp;quot;blueberry&amp;quot;:
    print(&amp;quot;Eating...&amp;quot;)
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;math&#34;&gt;Math&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In-line math: $x + y = z$&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Block math:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;$$
f\left( x \right) = \;\frac{{2\left( {x + 4} \right)\left( {x - 4} \right)}}{{\left( {x + 4} \right)\left( {x + 1} \right)}}
$$&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;fragments&#34;&gt;Fragments&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Make content appear incrementally&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;{{% fragment %}} One {{% /fragment %}}
{{% fragment %}} **Two** {{% /fragment %}}
{{% fragment %}} Three {{% /fragment %}}
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Press &lt;code&gt;Space&lt;/code&gt; to play!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;fragment &#34; &gt;
  One
&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&#34;fragment &#34; &gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;Two&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&#34;fragment &#34; &gt;
  Three
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A fragment can accept two optional parameters:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;class&lt;/code&gt;: use a custom style (requires definition in custom CSS)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;weight&lt;/code&gt;: sets the order in which a fragment appears&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;speaker-notes&#34;&gt;Speaker Notes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Add speaker notes to your presentation&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-markdown&#34;&gt;{{% speaker_note %}}
- Only the speaker can read these notes
- Press `S` key to view
{{% /speaker_note %}}
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Press the &lt;code&gt;S&lt;/code&gt; key to view the speaker notes!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;aside class=&#34;notes&#34;&gt;
  &lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Only the speaker can read these notes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Press &lt;code&gt;S&lt;/code&gt; key to view&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;/aside&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;themes&#34;&gt;Themes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;black: Black background, white text, blue links (default)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;white: White background, black text, blue links&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;league: Gray background, white text, blue links&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;beige: Beige background, dark text, brown links&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;sky: Blue background, thin dark text, blue links&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;night: Black background, thick white text, orange links&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;serif: Cappuccino background, gray text, brown links&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;simple: White background, black text, blue links&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;solarized: Cream-colored background, dark green text, blue links&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;


&lt;section data-noprocess data-shortcode-slide
  
      
      data-background-image=&#34;/img/boards.jpg&#34;
  &gt;


&lt;h2 id=&#34;custom-slide&#34;&gt;Custom Slide&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Customize the slide style and background&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-markdown&#34;&gt;{{&amp;lt; slide background-image=&amp;quot;/img/boards.jpg&amp;quot; &amp;gt;}}
{{&amp;lt; slide background-color=&amp;quot;#0000FF&amp;quot; &amp;gt;}}
{{&amp;lt; slide class=&amp;quot;my-style&amp;quot; &amp;gt;}}
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;custom-css-example&#34;&gt;Custom CSS Example&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;rsquo;s make headers navy colored.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Create &lt;code&gt;assets/css/reveal_custom.css&lt;/code&gt; with:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-css&#34;&gt;.reveal section h1,
.reveal section h2,
.reveal section h3 {
  color: navy;
}
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;questions&#34;&gt;Questions?&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://discourse.gohugo.io&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Ask&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://sourcethemes.com/academic/docs/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Documentation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
